<hits>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="852">« C'est encore pire que cela si vous prenez en compte le fondamentalisme religieux d'Erdogan » Y a-t-il d'autres fondamentalistes religieux au pouvoir au Moyen-Orient ?</source>
      <reference>"Its worse than that when you factor in Erdogan's religious fundamentalism" Are there any other religious fundamentalist leaders in the Middle East?</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">"It's even worse that that if you take into account the religious fundamentalism of Erdogan" are there other religious fundamentalists in power in the Middle East?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">"It's even worse than that if you take into account religious fundamentalism Erdogan" Will there other religious fundamentalists to power in the Middle East?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">"This is even worse than that if you take into account the religious fundamentalism of Erdogan:" are there any other religious fundamentalists in power in the Middle East?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">"It is even worse than that if you take into account the religious fundamentalism of Erdogan" Are there other religious fundamentalists in power in the Middle East?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">"it's even worse than that if you take into account the religious fundamentalism of Erdogan" Are there any other religious fundamentalists in power in the Middle East?</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="943">Ils développent l'un et l'autre des raisonnements très rationnels, mais cette rationalité repose sur ces boucs émissaires qui sont la clef de voûte de leur pensée.</source>
      <reference>They both develop very rational lines of argument, but this rationality is based on these scapegoats, which are the keystone of their thoughts.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">They are both very rational arguments, but this rationality is based on those scapegoats who are the cornerstone of their thinking.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">They develop the one and the other of the very rational reasonings, but this rationality rests on these scapegoats that are the key of arch of their thought.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">They develop both very rational reasoning but this rationality is based on these scapegoats are the keystone of their thinking.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">They develop one and other very rational reasoning, but this rationality is based on these scapegoats which are the keystone of their thinking.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">They develop one and the other of the very rational reasoning, but this rationality rests on these scapegoats which are the keystone of their thought.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="1290">Comme par exemple la Chine et l'Inde.</source>
      <reference>China and India come to mind.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">For example, China and India.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Such as China and India.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Such as for example China and India.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Like for example China and the India.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">As for example China and India.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="738">Amazon 30 £ pour PC, 35 £ pour Xbox 360 et PS3, 44 £ pour Xbox et PS4</source>
      <reference>Amazon £30 for PC £35 xbox 360 &amp; PS3 £44 for xbone &amp; PS4</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">Amazon 30£for PC, 35£for Xbox 360 and PS3, 44£for Xbox and PS4</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">Amazon 30 £ for PC, 35 £ for Xbox 360 and PS3, 44 £ for Xbox and PS4</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Amazon £30 to £35 for PC, Xbox 360 and PS3, Xbox and PS4 for £44</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">Amazon £30 to £35 for PC, Xbox 360 and PS3, Xbox and PS4 for £35 - 44</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Amazon £30 for PC, £35 for Xbox 360 and PS3, £44 for Xbox and PS4</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="378">Il aurait dû amener avec lui son ami le parpaing, plus intelligent que lui</source>
      <reference>Should have taken His smarter friend the House Brick with Him</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">He would have had to bring with him his friend, the smarter than him</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">It should have brought with him his friend the parpaing, more intelligent than him</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">He would have had to bring his friend the cinderblock, smarter than him</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">He should have brought with him his friend concrete blocks, smarter than him</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">He should bring with him his friend the cinder block, more intelligent than him</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="933">L'inutilité de glisser un bulletin dans une urne tous les 5 ans m'énerve profondément vu que mon vote ne compte vraiment pour rien.</source>
      <reference>I deeply resent the pointlessness of a cross on a piece of paper every 5 years when my vote doesn't even bloody well count.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">The futility of slip a ballot into a ballot box every 5 years irritates me deeply because my vote really counts for nothing.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">The uselessness of dragging a ballot paper in a ballot box every 5 years upsetting me deeply as my vote does not really count for nothing.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">Uselessness slipping a bulletin into a ballot box every 5 years irritates me deeply considering my vote really does not count for nothing.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">The futility of slipping a ballot paper in a ballot box every 5 years deeply irritates me because my vote really counts for nothing.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">The futility of slipping a ballot paper in a ballot box every 5 years me deeply because my vote doesn't really count for nothing.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="1105">A quand l'interdiction des syndicats dans les secteurs déjà protégés ?</source>
      <reference>When will unions be prohibited in already protected sectors?</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">When will the prohibition of trade unions in areas already protected?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">When will the banning of trade unions in the areas already protected?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">When the prohibition of trade unions in sectors already protected?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">When will the ban on trade unions in the areas already protected?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">With when the prohibition of the trade unions in the already protected sectors?</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="832">Chez votre libraire grand public, vous remarquerez systématiquement que tout le monde donne sa carte de fidélité (fn*c, d**itre, …).</source>
      <reference>At your large public bookseller, you will systematically notice that everyone gives their loyalty card (fn*c, d**itre, …).</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Your local bookseller general public, you'll notice that everyone gives its loyalty card (fn * c, d * * arena, ...).</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Your bookseller general public, you always notice that everyone gives its loyalty card (fn * c, d ** ter ...).</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">In your bookseller general public, you will notice systematically that everyone gives its loyalty card (fn*c, D ** itre,…).</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">From your local bookseller public, you will notice that everyone else is always gives his loyalty card (fn * c, d * * inhaled,...).</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">With your bookseller general public, you systematically will notice that everyone gives his fidelity card (fn*c, d**itre, …).</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="418">Un peu de nationalisme excessif, en fait.</source>
      <reference>A bit of excessive nationalism, basically.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">A little excessive nationalism, actually.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">A bit of excessive nationalism, in fact.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">A little excessive nationalism, in fact.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">A bit of excessive nationalism, actually.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="453">Pas tout le monde.</source>
      <reference>Not everyone.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Not the whole world.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">Not everyone else.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">Not everyone.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="1419">Regardez à nouveau et laisser l'image parler d'elle-même, sans la comparer au genre de dessin que vous préférez peut-être.</source>
      <reference>Have another look and let the picture speak for itself - not as a comparison to the type of drawing that you perhaps prefer.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Look again and let the image speak for itself, without comparing it to the kind of drawing that you may prefer.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">Look at again and to let the image speak about itself, without comparing it with the kind of drawing which you perhaps prefer.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Look again and let the picture speak for itself, without comparing it to the kind of design you might prefer.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">Look again and let the image speak for itself, without comparing it to the kind of design that you may prefer.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">Look at again and leave the picture to talk about itself, without comparing to it the drawing kind that you prefer maybe.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="439">C'est la seule voie.</source>
      <reference>This is the only way.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">This is the only way.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">It is the only way.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="862">Une maîtrise impressionnante du sophisme de la pente fatale, mais à part ça, on cherche en vain le contact avec le réel.</source>
      <reference>An impressive mastery of the slippery slope sophism, but apart from that, one searches in vain for the contact with what is real.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">An impressive control of the sophism of the fatal slope, but besides, one in vain seeks the contact with reality.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">An impressive mastery of the sophisme of the fatal slope, but to party that, one looks for in vain the contact with reality.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">An impressive mastery of the fatal slope fallacy, but apart from that, we are trying in vain to contact with the real world.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">An impressive command of the fallacy of the fatal slope, but other than that, it looks in vain for the contact with the real.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">An impressive mastery of the fallacy of the fatal slope, but apart from that, we look in vain for the contact with the real world.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="518">Comment ça vous n’avez pas envie de vous coltiner des chiards mal éduqués dont les parents vous crachent dessus en vous traitant de branleur ?</source>
      <reference>How does that not make you want to put up with poorly educated brats whose parents spit on you treating you like a little shit?</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">How that don't you want to carry you badly educated brats whose parents spit you above by treating you of wanker?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">How does it you don't want to carry the chiards poorly educated, whose parents are spitting on treating you wanker?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">What do you mean you don't want to carry the poorly educated chiards whose parents are spitting on top you in dealing with wanker?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">How is it you don't feel like you carry chiards of poorly educated, whose parents are spitting uppers of treating you wanker?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">What, you do not want to wrestle you poorly educated chiards whose parents spit on you by treating you wanker?</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="510">Ce n’est jamais le moment de renforcer l’éducation, car nous sommes toujours en guerre.</source>
      <reference>It is never the moment to strengthen education, as we are still at war.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">It's never the time to strengthen education, because we are still at war.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Is never the time to strengthen education, because we are still at war.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">It is never the time to strengthen education, because we are always at war.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">This is never the moment to reinforce the education, for we always are at war.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">It is never the moment to reinforce education, because we are always in war.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="782">Lisez un peu Bouddha et vous comprendrez à quel point vous faites erreur, cher Christian.</source>
      <reference>Read a little Buddha and you will understand to what extent you are making a mistake, dear Christian.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">Read a little Buddha and you will understand how you are wrong, dear Christian.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">Read a little Buddha and you will understand how much you are wrong, Mr Christian.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Read a little Buddha and you will understand how you are mistaken, dear Christian.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">Read a little Buddha and you will understand at which point you make error, dear Christian.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Read a little Buddha and you will understand how wrong you are, dear Christian.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="391">Une opération de com de plus ni fait ni a faire.</source>
      <reference>Another communication plan that is no longer done nor should be done.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">An operation of com or fact nor has more to do.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">An operation to com more and no facts or has to do.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">An operation of com over neither fact nor to do.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">A com operation done neither more nor to do.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">An operation of com of does more or do does or have to do.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="1402">Apparemment, personne ne veut regarder cette girafe en face.</source>
      <reference>Apparently, no one can see the giraffe in the room.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">Apparently, nobody wants to look at this giraffe opposite.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">Apparently, nobody wants to watch this giraffe in the face.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Apparently, no one wants to watch this giraffe face.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Apparently, nobody wants to watch this giraffe in front.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Apparently, no one wants to watch this giraffe in front.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="1059">tous ces immigrants somaliens qui viennent ici et attaquent nos péniches…</source>
      <reference>all those Somali immigants, coming over here, taking our canal boats ...</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">all these Somali immigrants who come here and attack our houseboats...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">all these somalian immigrants that come here and attack our barges…</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">All of these Somali immigrants who come here and attack our barges...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">all these Somali immigrants who come here and attack our barges…</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">All of these Somali immigrants who come here and attack our boats...</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="598">La notion d'écart entre riches et pauvres est subsidiaire.</source>
      <reference>The notion of the gap between rich and poor is subsidiary.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">The concept of difference between rich person and the poor is subsidiary.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">The concept of the gap between rich and poor is the alternative.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">The notion of the gap between rich and poor is subsidiary.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">The gap notion between rich and poor is subsidiary.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">The concept of the gap between rich and poor is subsidiary.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="162">Cette soudaine apparition de la lune rouge avait son charme et a compensé un peu la déception d'avoir parfois la vue bloquée par les nuages.</source>
      <reference>This sudden appearance of the red Moon had its charm, and somewhat compensated for the disappointment of clouds completely blocking the view at times.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">This sudden appearance of the red moon had its charm and compensated for disappointment a little to have sometimes the sight blocked by the clouds.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">This sudden appearance of the red moon had its charm and offset some of the disappointment sometimes have the view blocked by the clouds.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">This sudden one appearance of the red moon had his charm and compensated a little the disappointment of sometimes to have seen it blocked by the clouds.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">This sudden emergence of the red moon had his charm and offset a bit disappointed to have to sometimes blocked by clouds.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">This sudden emergence of the red moon had its charm and offset a bit of a disappointment to sometimes be blocked by clouds.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="940">Il puise dans un discours politique qui existe depuis des générations, mais qui a été marginalisé par les médias traditionnels - y compris le Guardian - depuis des générations.</source>
      <reference>He taps into a political narrative that exists through the generations, but which has been marginalised by mainstream media - including the Guardian - for generations.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">It draws from a political discourse that has existed for generations but which has been marginalized by the traditional media - including the Guardian - for generations.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">It draws in a political discourse that has existed for generations, but who has been marginalized by the traditional media - including the Guardian - for generations.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">He draws from a political discourse that has existed for generations, but which has been marginalized by the traditional media - including the Guardian - for generations.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">It draws in a political speech that exists since generations, but that was marginalized by the traditional media - including the Guardian - since generations.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">He draws from a political discourse that has existed for generations, but who was marginalized by mainstream media - including the Guardian - for generations.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="115">Le besoin d'infrastructures est marginal donc en rien un new deal pourrait être une solution.</source>
      <reference>The need for infrastructure is marginal, therefore in no way would a new deal be a solution.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">The need for infrastructure is marginal so nothing a new deal could be a solution.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">The need for infrastructure is marginal, therefore, in a new deal could be a solution.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">The need for infrastructure is marginal in no way a new deal could be a solution.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">The infrastructure need is marginal therefore in nothing a new deal could be a solution.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">The need for infrastructure is so marginal in any way a new deal could be a solution.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="1397">Et bien vous êtes en mesure de comprendre le concept du boboécolo.</source>
      <reference>Well then, you are in a position to understand the eco-boho concept.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">And while you are capable of understanding the concept of boboécolo.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Well you are able to understand the concept of boboécolo.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">And well you are able to understand the concept of the boboécolo.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">And while you are able to understand the concept of boboécolo.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">And well you are able to understand the concept of the boboecolo.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="361">Je ne comprends pas qu'on puisse penser que Boris ferait un bon leader pour les Conservateurs.</source>
      <reference>I don't understand why anyone thinks Boris will make a good Tory Leader.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">I do not understand how anyone can think that Boris would make a good leader for the Conservatives.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">I do not understand that one can think that Boris would make a good leader for the Conservatives.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">I don't understand that we can think that Boris would make a good leader for the Conservatives.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">I don't understand how you can think that Boris would make a good leader for the Conservatives.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">I do not understand that you may think that Boris would be a good leader for the Conservatives.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="108">Il y a aussi le bailleur qui vit des revenus de ses propriétés.</source>
      <reference>There is also the lessor who lives off the revenue from his properties.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">There is also the financial backer who lives incomes of his properties.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">There is also the lessor who lives on income from its properties.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">There is also the landlord who lives on income from properties.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">There is also the landlord who lives of income from its properties.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">There is also the landlord who lives income from its properties.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="867">Quant aux enfants!</source>
      <reference>As for the children!</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">As for the children!</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="800">Votre position est intellectuellement honnête mais pragmatiquement intenable.</source>
      <reference>Your position is intellectually honest but pragmatically indefensible.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">Your position is intellectually honest but pragmatically intolerable.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Your position is intellectually honest but pragmatically untenable.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="1465">Traduisez : Eoliennes et fermes solaires sont les Rond points de demain.</source>
      <reference>You translate: Wind turbines and solar farms are the roundabouts of tomorrow.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Translate: Wind and closed solar are the points of the future round.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Translate: Wind turbines and solar farms are the Round points tomorrow.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">Translate: Solar wind mills and farms are the Round points of tomorrow.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Translate: room and solar farms are the Rond points tomorrow.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">Translate: Wind turbines and solar farms are the Rond points tomorrow.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="487">Vérifiez votre assurance avant de louer votre maison.</source>
      <reference>Check your insurance before letting your home.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Check your insurance before you rent your home.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">Check your insurance before renting your house.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">Verify your assurance before renting your house.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">Please check your insurance before renting your home.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Check your insurance before you rent your house.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="49">Mais sans ce genre d'entreprises irlandaises, vous ne pourriez pas vous permettre de partir en vacances, jeune homme</source>
      <reference>Only for Irish companies like this you couldn't afford to go on hols young man</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">But without this kind of Irish business, you can't afford to go on holiday, young man</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">But without this kind of Irish companies, you couldn't afford to go on holiday, young man</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">But without this kind of Irish businesses, you could not allow you to leave on vacation, young man</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">But without this sort of Irish business, you can't afford to go on vacation, young man</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">But without this kind of Irish companies, you could not afford to go on vacation, young man</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="854">Il faudrait un procès de Nuremberg pour le génocide arménien commis par les Turcs.</source>
      <reference>There should be a Nuremberg trial for Turkish genocide of Armenians.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Should be a Nuremberg trial for the Armenian genocide committed by the Turks.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">It would be necessary a process of Nuremberg for the Armenian genocide committed by the Turks.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">One would need a lawsuit of Nuremberg for the Armenian genocide made by the Turks.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">There should be a Nuremberg trial for the Armenian genocide committed by the Turks.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">It should be a Nuremberg trial for the Armenian genocide committed by the Turks.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="768">C'est mercredi !</source>
      <reference>It's Wednesday!</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">It is Wednesday!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">It is on Wednesday!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">It's Wednesday!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">This is Wednesday!</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="1217">Le but est encore une fois de nous maintenir suffisamment effrayés et angoissés (sans en arriver à l'hystérie) pour le gouvernement puisse nous faire déraper quand il en a besoin.</source>
      <reference>It is all a part of keeping fear and anxiety levels high enough (but below hysteria) so that the govt can tip you over the edge when they need it.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">The aim is once again to keep us sufficiently frightened and anxious (without going to hysteria) for the government to make us go awry when he needs it.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">The aim is again to keep us sufficiently frightened and anxious (without coming to hysteria) for the government to derail us when he needs it.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">The goal is once more to maintain us sufficiently frightened and anxious (without some to arrive to hysteria) for the government can do us to slip when it has need of it.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">The goal is once again to maintain us sufficiently frightened and distressed (without coming to hysteria) for the government can make us skid when it needs some.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">The goal is once again to keep us frightened and anxious enough (without arriving at the hysteria) to enable the government to make us go awry when he needs it.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="1245">C'était une série géniale et on dirait que ceux qui la ressortent en ont conscience !</source>
      <reference>It was a wonderful series and it seems to being brought back by people who recognise that!</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">It was a great series and it seems like the ones that stand out are aware!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">It was an inspired series and one would say that those that the springs in are aware!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">It was a brilliant series, and it seems that those who are aware of it!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">It was a brilliant series and it would be said that those which arise it in are aware!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">It was a brilliant series and it seems that those who are aware of!</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="886">Je crois que dans la section des sports il y a un article sur le foot qui attend vos commentaires.</source>
      <reference>I think there's some football stories for you to comment on in the Sports section.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">I believe that in the section of the sports there is an item on the soccer that awaits your commentaries.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">I believe that in the section of the sports there is an article on the football which expects your comments.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">I believe that in the sports section there is an article about football awaits your comments.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">I believe that in the sports section there is an article about football that awaits your comments.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">I believe that in the sports section there is an article on football that awaits your comments.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="1027">Ah ça c'est pas de la langue de bois, plutôt en béton et armée la dame...</source>
      <reference>Ah this is not wooden language, but the woman has rather a concrete and reinforced one...</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">Oh ça c'est pas de la langue de bois, concrete rather than army and the lady...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">Oh it's not de la langue de bois, rather concrete and army the lady...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Looks like is not the language of wood, rather than concrete and army the lady...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">Ah that this is not language of wood, rather in concrete and army the lady...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Ah that's not the language of wood, concrete and army rather the lady ...</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="411">Je sais qu'il a perdu sa place lorsque Conte est arrivé, puis il est allé au Fener et autant que je sache il n'y est pas titulaire.</source>
      <reference>I know he lost his place when Conte arrived, then he moved to Fener, and as far as I know he isn't regular there.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">I know that he has lost his place when Conte has arrived, and then he went to the city and as far as I am aware there is no incumbent.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">I know he lost his place when Conte arrived, and then he went to Fener and AFAIK there is no owner.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">I know that he has lost his place when Conte has arrived, and then he went to Fener and as far as I know there is no incumbent.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">I know that it lost his place when Tells arrived, then it went to the Fener and as much as I know it there is not tenured.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">I know he has lost his place when Conte arrived, then he went to the Fener and as far as I know there is no incumbent.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="1212">Vous confondez Ébola et Murdoch...</source>
      <reference>You're confusing ebola with murdoch....</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">You are confusing Ebola and Murdoch...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">You confuse Ébola and Murdoch...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">You confuse Ebola and Murdoch...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">You confuse Ébola and Murdoch…</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="945">Cela relève d'une pensée très archaïque, la pensée sacrificielle, qui est aussi la pensée magique.</source>
      <reference>This stems from a very archaic way of thinking, sacrificial thinking, which is also magic thinking.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">This is part of a very archaic thinking, sacrificial thinking, which is also magical thinking.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">This is a very old fashioned thinking, the sacrificial thinking, which is also the magical thinking.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">This is a very archaic thinking, the sacrificial thinking, which is also a magical thinking.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">That concerns a very antiquated thought, the sacrificial thought, which is also the magic thought.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">That raises of a very archaic thought, the sacrificial thought, that also is thought it magic.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="657">Presque exactement 30 % de mon argent est prélevé à la source avant les impôts locaux et la vignette automobile.</source>
      <reference>Almost exactly 30% of my money is taken at source before council tax and road tax.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">Almost exactly 30% of my money is removed to the source before the local taxes and the label automobile.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Almost exactly 30% of my money is levied at source before local taxes and the vignette automobile.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Almost exactly 30% of my money is collected at the source before local taxes and auto thumbnail.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">Almost exactly 30% of my money are taken with the source before the local taxes and the automobile label.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">Almost exactly 30% of my money is deducted at source before the local taxes and the car sticker.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="346">Merci Passeur de sciences de nous régaler, souvent, de ces prouesses expérimentales qui sont réalisées dans le monde.</source>
      <reference>Thank you Passeur de sciences for treating us, often, to these experimental feats which are achieved in the world.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Thanks smuggler of sciences regale us, often, these experimental prowess which are carried out in the world.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">Thank you Frontier runner for sciences to level us, often, of these experimental prowesses which are carried out in the world.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">Thank you Smuggler of sciences to treat us, often, of these experimental prowess that are realized in the world.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Thank you load of science to regale us, often, of these experimental prowess which are carried out in the world.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Thank you Treader Sciences regale us often these experimental feats are performed worldwide.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="1444">Je crois qu'ils vont en faire un film.</source>
      <reference>I gather there's now a film with that title.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">I think they'll make a movie.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">I believe that they will make a film of it.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">I think they'll make it into a film.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">I believe that they go to do a film.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">I think they are going to make a movie.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="1438">Quant aux collectivités locales, l 'histoire se répète à chaque fermeture de poste, maternité, hôpital, caserne.</source>
      <reference>As for the local communities, history repeats itself with each post, maternity, hospital, barracks closure.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">As for local communities, history repeats itself at each station closures, maternity hospital, barracks.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">With respect to local communities, history repeats itself every closure of post, maternity, hospital, fire station.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">As for local communities, the story is repeated at each station closures, maternity, hospital, fire station.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">As for the local groups, l 'history repeats itself to every closing of post, maternity, hospital, quarters.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">As for local governments, history repeats itself at each station closing, maternity hospital, barracks.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="605">Le problème ce n'est pas le prix mais le capital politique des gouvernements occidentaux qui veulent prouver le vieil adage selon lequel les pervers colorés sont l'incarnation du mal.</source>
      <reference>The prize isn't its the political capital from western governments wanting to prove the old adage of deviant darkies being evil evil evil.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">The problem is not the price, but the political capital of the Western governments who want to prove the old adage that the coloured perverts are the embodiment of evil.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">The problem is not the price but the political capital of western governments who want to prove the old adage that coloured the transgressors are the embodiment of evil.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">The problem is not the price but the capital policy of Western governments who want to prove the old adage that colorful perverts are the embodiment of evil.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">The problem is not the price but the political capital of Western governments who want to prove the old adage that the colored perverse are the embodiment of evil.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">The problem this is not the price but the capital politics of the western governments that want to prove the old adage according to which the perverse colored ones are the incarnation of the evil.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="1027">Ah ça c'est pas de la langue de bois, plutôt en béton et armée la dame...</source>
      <reference>Ah this is not wooden language, but the woman has rather a concrete and reinforced one...</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">Oh ça c'est pas de la langue de bois, concrete rather than army and the lady...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">Oh it's not de la langue de bois, rather concrete and army the lady...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Looks like is not the language of wood, rather than concrete and army the lady...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">Ah that this is not language of wood, rather in concrete and army the lady...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Ah that's not the language of wood, concrete and army rather the lady ...</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="411">Je sais qu'il a perdu sa place lorsque Conte est arrivé, puis il est allé au Fener et autant que je sache il n'y est pas titulaire.</source>
      <reference>I know he lost his place when Conte arrived, then he moved to Fener, and as far as I know he isn't regular there.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">I know that he has lost his place when Conte has arrived, and then he went to the city and as far as I am aware there is no incumbent.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">I know he lost his place when Conte arrived, and then he went to Fener and AFAIK there is no owner.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">I know that he has lost his place when Conte has arrived, and then he went to Fener and as far as I know there is no incumbent.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">I know that it lost his place when Tells arrived, then it went to the Fener and as much as I know it there is not tenured.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">I know he has lost his place when Conte arrived, then he went to the Fener and as far as I know there is no incumbent.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="1212">Vous confondez Ébola et Murdoch...</source>
      <reference>You're confusing ebola with murdoch....</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">You are confusing Ebola and Murdoch...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">You confuse Ébola and Murdoch...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">You confuse Ebola and Murdoch...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">You confuse Ébola and Murdoch…</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="1217">Le but est encore une fois de nous maintenir suffisamment effrayés et angoissés (sans en arriver à l'hystérie) pour le gouvernement puisse nous faire déraper quand il en a besoin.</source>
      <reference>It is all a part of keeping fear and anxiety levels high enough (but below hysteria) so that the govt can tip you over the edge when they need it.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">The aim is once again to keep us sufficiently frightened and anxious (without going to hysteria) for the government to make us go awry when he needs it.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">The aim is again to keep us sufficiently frightened and anxious (without coming to hysteria) for the government to derail us when he needs it.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">The goal is once more to maintain us sufficiently frightened and anxious (without some to arrive to hysteria) for the government can do us to slip when it has need of it.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">The goal is once again to maintain us sufficiently frightened and distressed (without coming to hysteria) for the government can make us skid when it needs some.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">The goal is once again to keep us frightened and anxious enough (without arriving at the hysteria) to enable the government to make us go awry when he needs it.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="1245">C'était une série géniale et on dirait que ceux qui la ressortent en ont conscience !</source>
      <reference>It was a wonderful series and it seems to being brought back by people who recognise that!</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">It was a great series and it seems like the ones that stand out are aware!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">It was an inspired series and one would say that those that the springs in are aware!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">It was a brilliant series, and it seems that those who are aware of it!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">It was a brilliant series and it would be said that those which arise it in are aware!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">It was a brilliant series and it seems that those who are aware of!</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="886">Je crois que dans la section des sports il y a un article sur le foot qui attend vos commentaires.</source>
      <reference>I think there's some football stories for you to comment on in the Sports section.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">I believe that in the section of the sports there is an item on the soccer that awaits your commentaries.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">I believe that in the section of the sports there is an article on the football which expects your comments.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">I believe that in the sports section there is an article about football awaits your comments.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">I believe that in the sports section there is an article about football that awaits your comments.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">I believe that in the sports section there is an article on football that awaits your comments.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="1059">tous ces immigrants somaliens qui viennent ici et attaquent nos péniches…</source>
      <reference>all those Somali immigants, coming over here, taking our canal boats ...</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">all these Somali immigrants who come here and attack our houseboats...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">all these somalian immigrants that come here and attack our barges…</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">All of these Somali immigrants who come here and attack our barges...</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">all these Somali immigrants who come here and attack our barges…</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">All of these Somali immigrants who come here and attack our boats...</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="598">La notion d'écart entre riches et pauvres est subsidiaire.</source>
      <reference>The notion of the gap between rich and poor is subsidiary.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">The concept of difference between rich person and the poor is subsidiary.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">The concept of the gap between rich and poor is the alternative.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">The notion of the gap between rich and poor is subsidiary.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">The gap notion between rich and poor is subsidiary.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">The concept of the gap between rich and poor is subsidiary.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="162">Cette soudaine apparition de la lune rouge avait son charme et a compensé un peu la déception d'avoir parfois la vue bloquée par les nuages.</source>
      <reference>This sudden appearance of the red Moon had its charm, and somewhat compensated for the disappointment of clouds completely blocking the view at times.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">This sudden appearance of the red moon had its charm and compensated for disappointment a little to have sometimes the sight blocked by the clouds.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">This sudden appearance of the red moon had its charm and offset some of the disappointment sometimes have the view blocked by the clouds.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">This sudden one appearance of the red moon had his charm and compensated a little the disappointment of sometimes to have seen it blocked by the clouds.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">This sudden emergence of the red moon had his charm and offset a bit disappointed to have to sometimes blocked by clouds.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">This sudden emergence of the red moon had its charm and offset a bit of a disappointment to sometimes be blocked by clouds.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="940">Il puise dans un discours politique qui existe depuis des générations, mais qui a été marginalisé par les médias traditionnels - y compris le Guardian - depuis des générations.</source>
      <reference>He taps into a political narrative that exists through the generations, but which has been marginalised by mainstream media - including the Guardian - for generations.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">It draws from a political discourse that has existed for generations but which has been marginalized by the traditional media - including the Guardian - for generations.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">It draws in a political discourse that has existed for generations, but who has been marginalized by the traditional media - including the Guardian - for generations.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">He draws from a political discourse that has existed for generations, but which has been marginalized by the traditional media - including the Guardian - for generations.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">It draws in a political speech that exists since generations, but that was marginalized by the traditional media - including the Guardian - since generations.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">He draws from a political discourse that has existed for generations, but who was marginalized by mainstream media - including the Guardian - for generations.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="115">Le besoin d'infrastructures est marginal donc en rien un new deal pourrait être une solution.</source>
      <reference>The need for infrastructure is marginal, therefore in no way would a new deal be a solution.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">The need for infrastructure is marginal so nothing a new deal could be a solution.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">The need for infrastructure is marginal, therefore, in a new deal could be a solution.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">The need for infrastructure is marginal in no way a new deal could be a solution.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">The infrastructure need is marginal therefore in nothing a new deal could be a solution.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">The need for infrastructure is so marginal in any way a new deal could be a solution.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="1397">Et bien vous êtes en mesure de comprendre le concept du boboécolo.</source>
      <reference>Well then, you are in a position to understand the eco-boho concept.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">And while you are capable of understanding the concept of boboécolo.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Well you are able to understand the concept of boboécolo.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">And well you are able to understand the concept of the boboécolo.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">And while you are able to understand the concept of boboécolo.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">And well you are able to understand the concept of the boboecolo.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="49">Mais sans ce genre d'entreprises irlandaises, vous ne pourriez pas vous permettre de partir en vacances, jeune homme</source>
      <reference>Only for Irish companies like this you couldn't afford to go on hols young man</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">But without this kind of Irish business, you can't afford to go on holiday, young man</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">But without this kind of Irish companies, you couldn't afford to go on holiday, young man</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">But without this kind of Irish businesses, you could not allow you to leave on vacation, young man</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">But without this sort of Irish business, you can't afford to go on vacation, young man</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">But without this kind of Irish companies, you could not afford to go on vacation, young man</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="854">Il faudrait un procès de Nuremberg pour le génocide arménien commis par les Turcs.</source>
      <reference>There should be a Nuremberg trial for Turkish genocide of Armenians.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Should be a Nuremberg trial for the Armenian genocide committed by the Turks.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">It would be necessary a process of Nuremberg for the Armenian genocide committed by the Turks.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">One would need a lawsuit of Nuremberg for the Armenian genocide made by the Turks.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">There should be a Nuremberg trial for the Armenian genocide committed by the Turks.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">It should be a Nuremberg trial for the Armenian genocide committed by the Turks.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="768">C'est mercredi !</source>
      <reference>It's Wednesday!</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">It is Wednesday!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">It is on Wednesday!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">It's Wednesday!</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">This is Wednesday!</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="1105">A quand l'interdiction des syndicats dans les secteurs déjà protégés ?</source>
      <reference>When will unions be prohibited in already protected sectors?</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">When will the prohibition of trade unions in areas already protected?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">When will the banning of trade unions in the areas already protected?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">When the prohibition of trade unions in sectors already protected?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">When will the ban on trade unions in the areas already protected?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">With when the prohibition of the trade unions in the already protected sectors?</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="832">Chez votre libraire grand public, vous remarquerez systématiquement que tout le monde donne sa carte de fidélité (fn*c, d**itre, …).</source>
      <reference>At your large public bookseller, you will systematically notice that everyone gives their loyalty card (fn*c, d**itre, …).</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Your local bookseller general public, you'll notice that everyone gives its loyalty card (fn * c, d * * arena, ...).</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Your bookseller general public, you always notice that everyone gives its loyalty card (fn * c, d ** ter ...).</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">In your bookseller general public, you will notice systematically that everyone gives its loyalty card (fn*c, D ** itre,…).</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">From your local bookseller public, you will notice that everyone else is always gives his loyalty card (fn * c, d * * inhaled,...).</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">With your bookseller general public, you systematically will notice that everyone gives his fidelity card (fn*c, d**itre, …).</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="418">Un peu de nationalisme excessif, en fait.</source>
      <reference>A bit of excessive nationalism, basically.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">A little excessive nationalism, actually.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">A bit of excessive nationalism, in fact.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">A little excessive nationalism, in fact.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">A bit of excessive nationalism, actually.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="361">Je ne comprends pas qu'on puisse penser que Boris ferait un bon leader pour les Conservateurs.</source>
      <reference>I don't understand why anyone thinks Boris will make a good Tory Leader.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">I do not understand how anyone can think that Boris would make a good leader for the Conservatives.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">I do not understand that one can think that Boris would make a good leader for the Conservatives.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">I don't understand that we can think that Boris would make a good leader for the Conservatives.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">I don't understand how you can think that Boris would make a good leader for the Conservatives.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">I do not understand that you may think that Boris would be a good leader for the Conservatives.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="108">Il y a aussi le bailleur qui vit des revenus de ses propriétés.</source>
      <reference>There is also the lessor who lives off the revenue from his properties.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">There is also the financial backer who lives incomes of his properties.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">There is also the lessor who lives on income from its properties.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">There is also the landlord who lives on income from properties.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">There is also the landlord who lives of income from its properties.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">There is also the landlord who lives income from its properties.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="867">Quant aux enfants!</source>
      <reference>As for the children!</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">As for the children!</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="852">« C'est encore pire que cela si vous prenez en compte le fondamentalisme religieux d'Erdogan » Y a-t-il d'autres fondamentalistes religieux au pouvoir au Moyen-Orient ?</source>
      <reference>"Its worse than that when you factor in Erdogan's religious fundamentalism" Are there any other religious fundamentalist leaders in the Middle East?</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">"It's even worse that that if you take into account the religious fundamentalism of Erdogan" are there other religious fundamentalists in power in the Middle East?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">"It's even worse than that if you take into account religious fundamentalism Erdogan" Will there other religious fundamentalists to power in the Middle East?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">"This is even worse than that if you take into account the religious fundamentalism of Erdogan:" are there any other religious fundamentalists in power in the Middle East?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">"It is even worse than that if you take into account the religious fundamentalism of Erdogan" Are there other religious fundamentalists in power in the Middle East?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">"it's even worse than that if you take into account the religious fundamentalism of Erdogan" Are there any other religious fundamentalists in power in the Middle East?</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="943">Ils développent l'un et l'autre des raisonnements très rationnels, mais cette rationalité repose sur ces boucs émissaires qui sont la clef de voûte de leur pensée.</source>
      <reference>They both develop very rational lines of argument, but this rationality is based on these scapegoats, which are the keystone of their thoughts.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">They are both very rational arguments, but this rationality is based on those scapegoats who are the cornerstone of their thinking.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">They develop the one and the other of the very rational reasonings, but this rationality rests on these scapegoats that are the key of arch of their thought.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">They develop both very rational reasoning but this rationality is based on these scapegoats are the keystone of their thinking.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">They develop one and other very rational reasoning, but this rationality is based on these scapegoats which are the keystone of their thinking.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">They develop one and the other of the very rational reasoning, but this rationality rests on these scapegoats which are the keystone of their thought.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="1290">Comme par exemple la Chine et l'Inde.</source>
      <reference>China and India come to mind.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">For example, China and India.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">Such as China and India.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Such as for example China and India.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Like for example China and the India.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">As for example China and India.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="738">Amazon 30 £ pour PC, 35 £ pour Xbox 360 et PS3, 44 £ pour Xbox et PS4</source>
      <reference>Amazon £30 for PC £35 xbox 360 &amp; PS3 £44 for xbone &amp; PS4</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">Amazon 30£for PC, 35£for Xbox 360 and PS3, 44£for Xbox and PS4</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">Amazon 30 £ for PC, 35 £ for Xbox 360 and PS3, 44 £ for Xbox and PS4</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">Amazon £30 to £35 for PC, Xbox 360 and PS3, Xbox and PS4 for £44</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">Amazon £30 to £35 for PC, Xbox 360 and PS3, Xbox and PS4 for £35 - 44</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Amazon £30 for PC, £35 for Xbox 360 and PS3, £44 for Xbox and PS4</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="378">Il aurait dû amener avec lui son ami le parpaing, plus intelligent que lui</source>
      <reference>Should have taken His smarter friend the House Brick with Him</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">He would have had to bring with him his friend, the smarter than him</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">It should have brought with him his friend the parpaing, more intelligent than him</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">He would have had to bring his friend the cinderblock, smarter than him</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">He should have brought with him his friend concrete blocks, smarter than him</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">He should bring with him his friend the cinder block, more intelligent than him</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="933">L'inutilité de glisser un bulletin dans une urne tous les 5 ans m'énerve profondément vu que mon vote ne compte vraiment pour rien.</source>
      <reference>I deeply resent the pointlessness of a cross on a piece of paper every 5 years when my vote doesn't even bloody well count.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">The futility of slip a ballot into a ballot box every 5 years irritates me deeply because my vote really counts for nothing.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">The uselessness of dragging a ballot paper in a ballot box every 5 years upsetting me deeply as my vote does not really count for nothing.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">Uselessness slipping a bulletin into a ballot box every 5 years irritates me deeply considering my vote really does not count for nothing.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">The futility of slipping a ballot paper in a ballot box every 5 years deeply irritates me because my vote really counts for nothing.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">The futility of slipping a ballot paper in a ballot box every 5 years me deeply because my vote doesn't really count for nothing.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
  <hit block-id="-1" source-language="fre" target-language="eng">
    <seg>
      <source id="862">Une maîtrise impressionnante du sophisme de la pente fatale, mais à part ça, on cherche en vain le contact avec le réel.</source>
      <reference>An impressive mastery of the slippery slope sophism, but apart from that, one searches in vain for the contact with what is real.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">An impressive control of the sophism of the fatal slope, but besides, one in vain seeks the contact with reality.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">An impressive mastery of the sophisme of the fatal slope, but to party that, one looks for in vain the contact with reality.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">An impressive mastery of the fatal slope fallacy, but apart from that, we are trying in vain to contact with the real world.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">An impressive command of the fallacy of the fatal slope, but other than that, it looks in vain for the contact with the real.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">An impressive mastery of the fallacy of the fatal slope, but apart from that, we look in vain for the contact with the real world.</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="518">Comment ça vous n’avez pas envie de vous coltiner des chiards mal éduqués dont les parents vous crachent dessus en vous traitant de branleur ?</source>
      <reference>How does that not make you want to put up with poorly educated brats whose parents spit on you treating you like a little shit?</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">How that don't you want to carry you badly educated brats whose parents spit you above by treating you of wanker?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.LIMSI-CNRS-mosesSoulMoreFeatures.3999.fr-en.txt">How does it you don't want to carry the chiards poorly educated, whose parents are spitting on treating you wanker?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt">What do you mean you don't want to carry the poorly educated chiards whose parents are spitting on top you in dealing with wanker?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">How is it you don't feel like you carry chiards of poorly educated, whose parents are spitting uppers of treating you wanker?</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">What, you do not want to wrestle you poorly educated chiards whose parents spit on you by treating you wanker?</translation>
    </seg>
    <seg>
      <source id="510">Ce n’est jamais le moment de renforcer l’éducation, car nous sommes toujours en guerre.</source>
      <reference>It is never the moment to strengthen education, as we are still at war.</reference>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-B.0.fr-en.txt">It's never the time to strengthen education, because we are still at war.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-A.0.fr-en.txt">Is never the time to strengthen education, because we are still at war.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.uedin-jhu-phrase.4105.fr-en.txt,newsdiscusstest2015.UM-nDA.4036.fr-en.txt">It is never the time to strengthen education, because we are always at war.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-E.0.fr-en.txt">This is never the moment to reinforce the education, for we always are at war.</translation>
      <translation system="newsdiscusstest2015.online-F.0.fr-en.txt">It is never the moment to reinforce education, because we are always in war.</translation>
    </seg>
  </hit>
</hits>